Name: Kravchenko Liudmyla

Home address: Solom'yans'kyi district, Kyiv, Ukraine

Mobile number: +38 (050) 331-21-50 E-Mail: luisiya@gmail.com

Portfolio page:

https://luisiya.github.io/Kravchenko_Luisi/



Summary of qualifications:

I have been working as frontend-end developer freelancer for more than one year.

I've gained experience in building web application and services for commercial project of CRM system.

I have successfully applied my skills in Javascript, HTML5, Sass, WebPack. In order to advance my skills and knowledge, I have recently started studying React Fundamentals.

In addition, I have general skills in graphics editors, such as Photoshop and 3DStudio MAX. On previous positions I had an experience in design, development and administration of the database for the construction of BS network. I've successfully completed Harvard CS50 programming courses (BrainBasket Foundation).

Skills:

- JavaScript(ES5, ES6)
- HTML
- CSS/Sass
- Bootsrap
- Materialize

- Gulp
- Webpack
- C++ basics

GIT

- Agile business development and SCRUM
- Python basics

Work experience:

Freelance in Frontend-end development for commercial project of CRM System March 2017 – now

- Development of CRM System as an important part of a Scrum team.
- Implemented filters and sorting functionalities using JS in accordance with customer requirements.
- Render of the data using JS classes for dynamic generation of HTML table;
- Inline CRUD of table entries;
- Gulp/Webpack used;
- Facilitation of a team in a Scrum master role (part-time).
- Applying SCRUM ceremonies.
- The link to the demo version of the project: https://luisiya.github.io/crm_update/CRM_update/dist/html/

VF Ukraine (former Vodafone Ukraine), Kyiv, Ukraine

January 2010 - February 2017

Engineer of the 2nd category, Technical Directorate, Infrastructure Access Network Implementation Group

- Administration of the database for the construction of BS network;
- Participation in the modernization and improvement of the functionality of E-WorkOrder electronic system (preparation of requirement specification);
- Ensuring the implementation of the plan for the construction of base stations in the Central Region of Ukraine (control and management of timely project execution);
- Controlling of interaction processes between Territorial Offices and Contractors;

MTS Ukraine (former UMC), Kyiv, Ukraine

January 2010 – July 2005

Engineer, Project Management Department, BSS Development Department

- Coordination of GSM Network Expansion Project implementation with General Contractor;
- Control of implementation responsibilities by General Contractor according to the Turnkey Agreement;
- Project Management: Creation of centralized system of data handling, exchanging and saving all information and documentation concerning processes of building BS.

Golden Telecom, Account Manager July 2005 – September 2004

- Sales of services and subscriber equipment of fixed communication (telephony, data transfer, Internet);
- Holding negotiations with potential/existing clients, giving consultations on all the company's services.

Education:

• 2003-2004

State University of Information and Communication Technologies, **Master of Science Degree in Telecommunications with distinction**.

The main specialization is Technology of Switch Centers.

• 2000-2002

London school of English, Kiev, Ukraine.

Upper-intermediate course.

• 1999 - 2000

Bachelor of Science Degree in Telecommunications, State University of Information and Communications Technologies (Information Networks faculty); obtained a distinction.

Trainings / practice:

rrainings / practice.	
2018 REACT, GoIT	2018 Java Script, GolT
2017 HTML, CSS, SASS, Gulp GoIT	2017 Basic Algorithm Scripting, CodeAcademy
2017 CS50: Introduction to Computer Science	2017 Beginner's course of German, Language school
2016 Basic JavaScript, CodeAcademy	2016 Basic Front End Development Project, CodeAcademy
2016 jQuery, CodeAcademy	2016 HTML&CSS, CodeAcademy
2016 Business English, Prometheus school	2016 SQL Fundamentals, Codecademy
2015 Upper-Intermediate course of English	2012 SAP CFM, MTS, Kyiv
2007 Interface Russia, Planning, installation, configuration and administration Microsoft Office Project Server 2003	2007 Interface Russia, Special aspects of Project Management with MS Project
2006 Kvazar-Micro Education Center, Microsoft Access 2003	2005 IBM Russia, Project Management Fundamentals
2005 AcadEx, U14404 - IBM Lotus Notes 6 Course	2005 NAU Consulting Group, Technology of effective sales
2005 Golden Telecom, Account Manager School	2004 Sales Basics training, IIB

Additional information:

PC skills:	MS Windows, Word, Excel, Visio, Power Point, Access, Outlook, Lotus, SAP, 3DStudio MAX, SketchUp, HTML, CSS, SASS, JavaScript, C++ basics, Python basics, Git, Gulp, Adobe Photoshop, Sublime Text, WebStorm
Language skills:	Native Russian and Ukrainian, fluent English, German basics
Possible trips:	Biometric passport
Hobby:	Development, painting, running

Personal:

Date of birth:	January 20, 1981
Personal abilities:	Responsibility, highly-organized, good interpersonal skills, determination, creative, easy and quick learning, energetic, punctuality.